Inventory of the Nell Eurich papers 1922-2000
Hoover Institution Archives
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Vendors
    - Programs
      - Managers
        - Other companies, A to G, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 100: 12)
        - Other companies, L to W, 1987 (Box-folder 101: 1)
      - Professionals
        - Brochures and other literature, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 101: 2)
      - Missing persons
        - Compris Inc., undated (Box-folder 101: 3)
        - "I Want to Read,", 1988 (Box-folder 101: 4)
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - American Management Association (AMA) satellite seminars, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 101: 5)
      - Association for Media-Based Continuing Education for Engineers (AMCEE)
        - Monitor, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 101: 6)
        - Uplink, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 101: 7)
        - Annual catalogs, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 101: 8)
        - Other literature, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - Education
    - Vocational and technical
      - General, 1987 (Box-folder 102: 2)
      - Articles, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 102: 3)
      - Research studies, A to H, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 102: 4)
      - Research studies, K to R, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 102: 5)
      - Research studies, S to W, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 103: 1)
      - Other literature
        - National Assessment of Vocational Education (NAVE), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 103: 2)
        - National Center for Research in Vocational Education (NCRVE), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 103: 3)
        - National Occupations Information Coordinating Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 103: 4)
        - Open Entries, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 103: 5)
        - Vocational Technical Education Consortium of States (V-TECS), circa 1987 (Box-folder 103: 6)
        - Staff report, circa 1988 (Box-folder 103: 7)
          Possibly by Sarah White
        - Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 104: 1)
      - Proprietary schools
        - Statistics, circa 1984 (Box-folder 104: 2)
        - Carnegie Foundation database, 1986, undated (Box-folder 104: 3)
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 104: 4)
        - Articles, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 104: 5)
        - Research studies, A to M, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 104: 6)
        - Research studies, T to Y, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 104: 7)
        - Staff report by Sarah White, 1987 (Box-folder 104: 8)
        - Other literature
          - Accrediting Bureau of Health Education Schools (ABHES), 1979-1988, undated (Box-folder 104: 9)
          - Association of Independent Colleges and Schools (AICS), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 105: 1)
          - National Accrediting Commission of Cosmetology Arts and Sciences, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 105: 2)
- Corporate Classrooms file
  - Corporate colleges and institutions
    - Chart of corporate colleges, 1983-1984, undated (Box-folder 105: 3)
    - Arthur D. Little Management Education Institute, 1981-1999 (Box-folder 105: 4)
    - American Graduate School of International Management, circa 1982-1984 (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - American Institute of Banking at Boston, 1983 (Box-folder 105: 6)
    - American College, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - Boston Architectural Center School of Architecture, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 106: 2)
    - DeVry Institute of Technology, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 106: 3)
    - Edna McConnell Clark School of Nursing, undated (Box-folder 106: 4)
    - GMI Engineering and Management Institute, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 106: 5-6)
    - Industrial Management Institute, undated (Box-folder 106: 7)
    - Institute of Management Competency, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 106: 8)
    - Institute of Textile Technology, 1984, undated (Box-folder 106: 9)
    - College of Insurance, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 107: 1)
    - MGH Institute of Health Professions, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 107: 2)
    - McDonald's Management Institute, Hamburger University, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 107: 3)
    - Northrop University, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - Rand Graduate Institute
      - General, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 107: 5)
      - Books on history and activities, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - Wang Institute of Graduate Studies, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 108: 1)
    - Watterson College, main campus, 1982, undated (Box-folder 108: 2)
- Correspondence
  - Noteworthy correspondents
    - Ashby, Eric, 1966 (Box-folder 108: 3)
    - Barzun, Jacques, 1969-1993 (Box-folder 108: 4)
    - Britten, Benjamin, undated (Box-folder 108: 5)
    - Hall, Lee, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 108: 6)
    - Kenny, Shirley Strum, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - Schroeder, Patricia, 1996 (Box-folder 108: 8)
    - Reich, Robert, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 108: 9)
    - Toynbee, Arnold, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 108: 10)
  - General
    - 1992-1997 (Box-folder 108: 11-15)
    - 1985-1992 (Box-folder 109: 1-8)
      Includes attached letters from 1983 and 1984
    - 1964-1983 (Box-folder 110: 1-4)
      Includes invitations to Nell Eurich regarding presidencies
- Corporate Classrooms file
  - Distribution and publicity
    - Distribution, 1985, undated (Box-folder 110: 5)
    - Press release, 1985 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - Invitations declined, 1985 (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - Publicity
      - Contacts, undated (Box-folder 110: 8)
      - Publicity binder, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 110: 9)
        Includes clippings
      - National Technological University (NTU) Master of Science in Engineering Management brochure, undated (Box-folder 110: 10)
      - American School and University, 1985 (Box-folder 110: 11)
      - The Education Digest, 1985 (Box-folder 110: 12)
      - U.S. News and World Report, 1985 (Box-folder 110: 13)
      - Dallas Business Journal, 1986 (Box-folder 110: 14)
      - Self Magazine, 1986 (Box-folder 110: 15)
      - Analyses de la S.E.D.E.I.S., 1986-1988 (Box-folder 110: 16)
      - Glamour, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 17)
      - L. A. Times, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 18)
      - New York Times, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 19)
      - Training and Development Journal, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 20)
      - World, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 21)
      - Wall Street Journal, 1987 (Box-folder 110: 22)
  - Correspondence
    - 1985-1988 (Box-folder 111: 1)
    - 1981-1985 (Box-folder 111: 2)
    - Inquiries about training resources, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 111: 3)
- Collection overview and biographical file
  - Overview and container list, undated (Box-folder 111: 4)
    Includes curriculum vitae information of Nell Eurich within the container list. Includes one floppy disk.
  - Curriculum vitae of Nell Eurich, undated (Box-folder 111: 5)
- Speeches and writings
  - Books and book contributions
    - The Learning Industry: Education for Adult Workers, 1990 (Box-folder 111: 6)
      Includes signed dedication to Eurich from 1991
    - Corporate Classrooms: The Learning Business, 1985 (Box-folder 111: 7)
    - Systems of Higher Education in Twelve Countries: A Comparative View, 1981 (Box-folder 112: 1)
    - Systems of Higher Education, International Council for Education Development
      - Australia, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 2)
      - Canada, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 3)
      - Federal Republic of Germany, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 4)
      - Federal Republic of Germany, German translation, 1979 (Box-folder 112: 5)
      - France, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 6)
      - Iran, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 7)
      - Mexico, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 8)
      - Japan, photocopy, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 9)
      - Poland, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 10)
      - Sweden, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 1)
      - Thailand, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 2)
      - United Kingdom, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 3)
      - United States, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 4)
      - 12 Systems of Higher Education: 6 Decisive Issues, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 5)
    - Great Britain's Open University: First Chance, Second Chance, Last Chance?
      - Published booklet, 1971 (Box-folder 113: 6)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 113: 7)
      - Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 113: 8)
      - Drafts and notes, 1971, undated (Box-folder 113: 9)
      - Background, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 113: 10)
      - Follow up clippings and other literature, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 114: 1)
      - Humanities Foundation Course, printed matter, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 114: 2-4)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Bennington College
    - General, 1975-1987, undated (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - Budget and Finance Committee, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - Grants, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - Meeting minutes of trustees, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - Nominating Committee, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - Admissions Committee, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 115: 6-7)
    - Admissions Committee, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 116: 1-2)
  - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education
    - General, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - Notes on "3000 Futures" report, undated (Box-folder 116: 4)
    - Task force, federal-state-institutional relations, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 116: 5)
    - Federal relations to higher education, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 116: 6)
    - Miscellaneous papers on higher education, 1969-1984 (Box-folder 116: 7)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 116: 8)
    - Seminars, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 116: 9-10)
    - Iran workshop, 1977 (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - Japan Seminar, 1975 (Box-folder 116: 12)
    - Seminar notes, undated (Box-folder 117: 1)
    - Papers and articles, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 117: 2)
    - Articles by Harlan Cleveland, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 117: 3)
    - Bound course readings, 1979, undated (Box-folder 117: 4-5)
    - Bound course readings, 1979-1980, undated (Box-folder 118: 1-2)
  - New York University, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 118: 3)
  - Stephens College
    - Correspondence, 1941-1992 (Box-folder 118: 4)
    - Presidency, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 118: 5)
    - Academic and public service citation, 1962 (Box-folder 118: 6)
    - Stephens: A Story of Educational Innovation by John C. Crighton, 1970 (Box-folder 119: 1)
  - Women's Foundation
    - Correspondence
      - Letters from interested parties, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 119: 2)
      - Langmuir, Mary Fisher, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 119: 3)
      - Pennock, C. H. L., 1949-1950 (Box-folder 119: 4)
      - Anderson, A. N., 1950, undated (Box-folder 119: 5)
    - Proposal for James Madison Wood Institute for Women's Education at Stephens College, 1982 (Box-folder 119: 6)
    - Study, "A College for Women Past 40,", 1949-1951 (Box-folder 119: 7)
    - Vassar Summer Institute, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 119: 8)
    - Curriculum for "mature women,", 1949-1950 (Box-folder 119: 9)
    - 1948 White House conference on the American family, 1948, 1979 (Box-folder 119: 10)
      Organized by Nell Eurich
- Other activities file
  - Carnegie Corporation presidential search, 1982 (Box-folder 120: 1)
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York curriculum proposals, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 120: 2)
  - Notre Dame College faculty and trustee workshop, 1975 (Box-folder 120: 3)
    Includes remarks, most likely by Nell Eurich
  - Today Show panel, undated (Box-folder 120: 4)
  - Campobello Summer Student Leadership Institute with Eleanor Roosevelt (1941), 1941-1979 (Box-folder 120: 5)
    Includes photographs of Eleanor Roosevelt and students
  - Campobello Summer Student Leadership Institute 50th anniversary reunion (1992), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 120: 6)
  - Community service
    - Mailing lists, city agencies, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 120: 7)
    - Publicity clippings, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 120: 8)
    - Landmark Commission, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 120: 9-10)
    - Rizzoli and Coty Buildings, Fifth Avenue, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 11)
    - 17 & 24 Corporation Board of Directors, landmark and zoning, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 120: 12)
    - Developers of property, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 121: 1)
      Includes landmarks and preservation work
    - Committee for Preservation, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 121: 2)
    - Midtown development plan, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 121: 3)
    - City Planning Commission, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 121: 4)
    - National Register of Historic Places, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 121: 5)
  - Institute for Advanced Studies in Medicine and the Humanities, Naples, Florida
    - Naples Institute, 1976-1977, undated (Box-folder 121: 7)
    - Literature from the Hastings Center Institute of Society, Ethics, and the Life Sciences, 1977 (Box-folder 121: 8)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Rhodes Scholarships, Middle Atlantic Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 122: 1)
  - International Council for Educational Development
    - General
      - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 122: 2)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 122: 3)
      - 1992-1994 (Box-folder 122: 4)
      - Board meeting, Williamsburg, 1993 (Box-folder 122: 5)
      - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 122: 6)
      - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 122: 7)
      - 1988-1989 (Box-folder 122: 8)
      - Conference in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1983 (Box-folder 122: 9)
    - Systems of Higher Education in 12 Countries study
      - General, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 123: 1)
      - Study definitions, 1975-1976, undated (Box-folder 123: 2)
      - International conference notes, undated (Box-folder 123: 3)
      - Notes on European seminars, undated (Box-folder 123: 4)
      - Speech given by Clark Kerr in Uppsala, Sweden, 1977 (Box-folder 123: 5)
      - Printed matter, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 123: 6)
      - Country files
        - Australia
          - General, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 123: 7)
          - Speech by Nell Eurich, undated (Box-folder 123: 8)
        - Britain and Canada, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 123: 9)
        - Japan conference, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 123: 10)
        - Mexico, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 123: 11)
        - Poland
          - General, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 123: 12)
          - Polish seminar, 1979 (Box-folder 123: 13)
        - Sweden, 1978 (Box-folder 124: 1)
        - West Germany and France, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 124: 2)
      - Systems of Higher Education in 12 Countries: A Comparative View
        - Publication and distribution, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 124: 3)
        - Responses, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 124: 4)
  - United States Department of State, Career Minister Review Board, 1972 (Box-folder 125: 5)
    Includes photograph of Eurich and others being sworn in
- Speeches and writings
  - Books and book contributions
    - Science in Utopia
      - Monograph, 1967 (Box-folder 124: 6)
      - Distribution, publicity, and correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box-folder 124: 7)
      - Background and notes, 1973, undated (Box-folder 124: 8)
      - "Directory of Utopian Scholars,", 1986 (Box-folder 124: 9)
    - From Parnassus: A Volume of Essays for Jacques Barzun
      Contains the essay "Learning in America" by Nell Eurich
      - Monograph, 1967 (Box-folder 124: 10)
      - Typescript of "Learning in America" and correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 125: 1)
      - Criticism, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 125: 2)
    - Learning for Tomorrow
      Contains "The Humanities Face the Future" by Nell Eurich
      - Monograph, 1974 (Box-folder 125: 3)
      - Typescript of "The Humanities Face the Future" and publicity, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 125: 4)
  - Articles
    - "Training for High Performance in Industry," Journal of Cooperative Education (1994), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 125: 5)
    - "So Much Talk--Too Little Action," Public Agenda Foundation, 1991 August (Box-folder 125: 6)
    - "Learning for Productivity," Issues in Science and Technology, 1991 (Box-folder 125: 7)
    - "The Real Commencement for High School Students," NASSP Bulletin, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 125: 8)
    - "Continuing Education and the Learning Industry," The Journal of Continuing Higher Education, 1991 (Box-folder 125: 9)
    - "Learning by Networks," IBM, 1987 (Box-folder 125: 10)
    - "Corporate Colleges," Economic Impact, 1986 (Box-folder 125: 11)
    - "Corporate Classrooms and America's Schools," NASSP Bulletin and The Education Digest, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 125: 12)
    - "Needed: A Strategic Council for Educational Development," Book Forum, 1985 (Box-folder 125: 13)
    - "Has Industry Changed Education?" Bell Atlantic Quarterly, 1985 (Box-folder 125: 14)
    - "Remembering Conant's The American High School Today," Change, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - Articles published before 1980, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 126: 2)
  - Papers
    - "Corporate Classrooms: The Learning Business," European Foundation for Management Development, 15th anniversary meeting, Insead, Fontainebleau, France, 1986 (Box-folder 126: 3)
    - "Liberal Arts and Their Usefulness," Corporate Council on Liberal Arts Symposium, Harvard University, 1986 (Box-folder 126: 4)
    - "Corporate Models for Lifelong Learning," Alden Seminar, Weston, Massachusetts, 1986 (Box-folder 126: 5)
    - "Learners Without Classrooms," European Institute of Education and Social Policy, Paris, 1985 (Box-folder 126: 6)
    - "Students as Viewed by an Administrator," Higher Education and the Current Crisis, 1975 (Box-folder 126: 7)
      Presented at the 1975 Aspen Seminar
  - Speeches (Box-folder 126-127)
    - "Training for High Performance in Industry," Eighth World Conference on Cooperative Education, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 126: 8)
      See also box 127, folders 1-4
    - "Language and Literacy in Today's Culture," English Speaking Union
      - Drafts, 1994 (Box-folder 126: 9)
      - Note cards and printed matter, circa 1961-1994 (Box-folder 126: 10)
      - Footnotes, 1937-1994 (Box-folder 126: 11)
        Includes source material for footnotes
      - Source material, 1994 (Box-folder 126: 12)
      - Legislation, 1991-1994, undated (Box-folder 126: 13)
    - "Training for High Performance in Industry," Eighth World Conference on Cooperative Education, Dublin City University
      See also box 126, folder 8
      - Speech, 1993 (Box-folder 127: 1)
      - Footnotes, 1993 (Box-folder 127: 2)
      - Notes, conference literature, and correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 127: 3)
      - Adult training networks in Europe, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 127: 4)
- Corporate Classrooms file (Box-folder 127-130)
  - Corporate training programs
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Box-folder 127: 5)
    - Eli Lilly Company, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 127: 6)
    - Ford, retraining, 1984 (Box-folder 127: 7)
    - General Electric, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 127: 8)
    - Hewlett-Packard, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 127: 9)
    - Holiday Inn, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 127: 10)
    - International Business Machines (IBM)
      - Thornwood visit, 1986 (Box-folder 128: 1)
      - Eric Bloch, Systems Research Institute (SRI), Ralph Grubb, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 128: 2)
      - Corporate Institutes, 1983 (Box-folder 128: 3)
      - General, 1983 (Box-folder 128: 4)
      - La Hulpe and Europe, 1976-1986, undated (Box-folder 128: 5)
      - European Academic and Research Network (EARN) network, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 128: 6)
      - Executive Management Development, undated (Box-folder 128: 7)
      - Interactive Satellite Education Network (ISEN), undated (Box-folder 128: 8)
    - Japanese corporate training, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 128: 9)
      Includes correspondence with Nevser Stacy
    - Kimberly-Clark Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 128: 10)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 128: 11)
    - McGraw-Hill, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 128: 12)
    - Merrill Lynch, Donald T. Regan School, undated (Box-folder 128: 13)
    - Motorola, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 128: 14)
    - Motorola University catalog of training and education products and services, undated (Box-folder 129: 1)
    - Nalco Chemical Company, 1983 (Box-folder 129: 2)
    - NCR Corporation, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 129: 3)
    - New England Telephone Learning Center, 1983 (Box-folder 129: 4)
    - Polaroid, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 129: 5)
    - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 129: 6)
    - Standard Oil of California, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 129: 7)
    - Sun Institute, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 129: 8)
    - Texas Instruments
      - Computer literacy, 1983 (Box-folder 130: 1)
      - Dallas Metroplex reports, 1984 (Box-folder 130: 2)
      - Educational products, undated (Box-folder 130: 3)
      - General, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 130: 4)
    - Western Electric, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 130: 5)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Manhattanville College
    - General, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 130: 6)
    - Honorary degree, 1975 (Box-folder 130: 7)
    - "Manhattanville Plan" and background material, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 130: 8)
    - "Manhattanville Plan" and background (Contd.), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 131: 1)
    - "Mornings at Manhattanville" seminars, 1976 (Box-folder 131: 2)
    - Proposal for Humanities for Teachers program, undated (Box-folder 131: 3)
    - Faculty, 1975, undated (Box-folder 131: 4)
    - Dan Isaac case (Box-folder 131: 5)
      Case concerning religious discrimination and tenure
  - Academy for Educational Development
    - General, 1966-1991 (Box-folder 131: 6)
    - Jenkins, Davis, 1987 (Box-folder 131: 7)
    - Consultant report by Nell and Alvin Eurich, 1982 (Box-folder 131: 8)
    - President's office, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 131: 9)
    - Executive Search Division, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 132: 1)
    - Information and Learning Technologies Division, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 132: 2)
    - International Division, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 132: 3)
    - Library, undated (Box-folder 132: 4)
    - Office of Arts, 1988 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    - Office of Contract Management, 1988 (Box-folder 132: 6)
    - Private Sector Capability Statement, 1986 (Box-folder 132: 7)
    - Proposal, "The Status of the Third Sector in Post-Secondary Education,", 1981 (Box-folder 132: 8)
      Proposal concerning education provided to employees by employers
    - Kurt Moses training proposal to AT&T Bell Labs, 1985 (Box-folder 132: 9)
    - Paul T. Bucci report on Virginia funding program for undergraduate education, 1988 (Box-folder 132: 10)
  - Harvard University, Overseers Visiting Committee on Summer School and University Extension
    - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 132: 11)
    - Overseers Visiting Committee, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 132: 12-13)
    - Summer school catalogs, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 133: 1)
  - World Society for Ekistics, Delos Symposiums, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 133: 2)
  - U.S. Commission on Instructional Technology, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    - General, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 133: 3)
    - Articles, 1970 (Box-folder 133: 4)
  - New College
    - Meeting, 1984 (Box-folder 133: 5)
    - Commencement address, 1975 (Box-folder 133: 6)
    - Presidential candidates, 1975 (Box-folder 133: 7)
    - Nell Eurich's appointment as acting president, 1975 (Box-folder 133: 8)
    - Papers by David Riesman, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 133: 9)
    - Institutional self-study, 1970 (Box-folder 134: 1)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 134: 2-3)
    - John French, studies of student performance, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 134: 4)
    - Meetings and interim report, 1969 (Box-folder 135: 1)
    - Fundraising and budget, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 135: 2)
    - Faculty, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 135: 3)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1966 (Box-folder 135: 4)
    - Executive Committee, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 135: 5)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 135: 6)
    - Tenure policy and academic freedom, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 135: 7)
    - College publications, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 135: 8)
    - Residence halls, 1966, undated (Box-folder 135: 9)